Dogs are in high demand as pets.
作为宠物，狗的需求量很大。
In fact, 36% of households in the UK own one, according to the UK Pet Food survey 2024.
事实上，根据2024年英国宠物食品调查，英国36%的家庭养狗。
Our canine pals can be cute, cuddly and loyal friends.
我们的犬类伙伴可以是可爱、令人想拥抱且忠诚的朋友。
But, for many owners, dogs are much more than this – they are a lifeline.
但对许多主人来说，狗的意义远不止于此——它们是救生索。
Assistance dogs provide essential support, increased independence and companionship for disabled people and people with medical conditions – they have even saved lives.
辅助犬为残疾和患病人群提供必要的支持、提升他们的独立性并提供陪伴——它们甚至拯救过生命。
There are many different types of assistance dogs out there, from hearing dogs to autism dogs to guide dogs.
从助听犬到自闭症辅助犬再到导盲犬，有各种不同类型的辅助犬。
But what makes the perfect assistance dog?
但是，什么造就了完美的辅助犬呢？
Common assistance dog breeds are Labrador retrievers, golden retrievers and German shepherds.
常见的辅助犬品种有拉布拉多寻回犬、金毛寻回犬和德国牧羊犬。
The most common guide dog in the UK is the golden retriever-Labrador cross, which, according to the Guide Dogs National Centre, has a 'combination of desirable traits'.
英国最常见的导盲犬是金毛寻回犬与拉布拉多犬的杂交犬，据导盲犬国家中心称，这种犬具有"理想特征的组合"。
Guide dogs need to be able to lead a blind or visually impaired person outside and inside, while avoiding distractions and recognising and avoiding obstacles such as changes in elevation, like tree roots, curbs and stairs.
导盲犬需要能够引导盲人或视障人士在室内外行走，同时避免分心，识别并避开障碍物，例如高度变化，如树根、马路牙子和台阶。
With that in mind, training puppies is essential.
考虑到这一点，对幼犬的训练至关重要。
The Guide Dogs for the Blind Association trains puppies using positive reinforcement, rewarding good behaviour with food, praise and affection.
英国导盲犬协会使用积极强化法训练幼犬，用食物、表扬和关爱来奖励良好行为。
When it comes to hearing dogs, a very important part of their training is sound awareness – alerting their deaf partner to sounds they would otherwise miss, for example a smoke alarm, an alarm clock or a crying baby.
对于助听犬来说，它们训练中非常重要的一部分是声音意识——让聋人同伴注意到他们可能会错过的声音，例如烟雾报警器、闹钟或婴儿的哭声。
Katie Grundy, a puppy trainer at the charity Hearing Dogs for Deaf People, teaches puppies targeting, a technique where the dogs touch a target, like a hand, with their nose for a treat.
慈善机构"聋人助听犬"的幼犬训练师凯蒂·格伦迪教导幼犬进行目标训练，这是一种让狗用鼻子触碰目标（如手）以获得奖励的技巧。
This teaches hearing dogs how to notify their partner when a sound goes off.
这教会助听犬如何在声音响起时通知它们的同伴。
At the end of training, not all pups qualify, but they are put up for adoption and, of course, make excellent lovable pets.
训练结束时，并非所有幼犬都能合格，但它们会被送去领养，当然，它们会成为出色的、惹人喜爱的宠物。